SARAH BAHEJRI

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A committed and self-motivated consultant with 4+ years of experience in organizational development, operational excellence, strategic planning, and change management projects. Extremely adaptable and collaborative individual with a strong desire to learn, solve problems, and consistently achieve results for clients and internal teams.

EDUCATION

Effat University, Jeddah Bachelor of Science, Information Systems, 05/2017 GPA: 3.92/4.0

WORK HISTORY

CONSULTANT 01/2022 - Current

Baseqat Arabia Consulting, Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

- Managed HR consulting projects, ensuring effective scheduling, resource allocation, progress reporting, and timely completion of milestones
- Led project teams to deliver client solutions by planning and delegating tasks to team members, ensuring optimum quality
- Managed internal and external stakeholders for projects, including international experts, local vendors, or consortium partners
- Led Business Development activities, consisting of the development of Technical and Financial proposals to attract and reach more clients
- Led Knowledge Transfer sessions with clients to transfer expertise and ensure clients can implement knowledge effectively
- Provided strategic recommendations to optimize the work environment in the company, and trained junior consultants to maximize efficiency

ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT 04/2018 - 01/2022

Baseqat Arabia Consulting, Jeddah

- Designed the training & development processes and policies for SANS company.
- Developed competency-based training & career pathing programs and supported the development of a communication plan to launch these programs using "ADKAR framework" for Ministry of Finance.
- Developed behavioral competency framework and conducted real estate benchmarks for strategy development purposes for Pan Kingdom Real Estate company.
- Assessed and developed organizational structures & job descriptions for various clients in private and public sectors (e.g., MISA, Saudi Arabia Premium Residency Center, Ghaya Pharmacies, MAHD Academy, and Historic Jeddah Program).
- Evaluated jobs using (Mercer IPE Methodology) and developed salary scales for multiple clients (MAHD Sports Academy, MISA, etc.).

RESEARCH ASSISTANT 08/2017 - 09/2017

Futures Business Development, Jeddah

- Contributed to the identification of target audience segments by conducting marketing research
- Developed a marketing plan to promote a patent app online
- Developed an app navigation guide "walkthrough" for customers
- · Organized ambassadors' information in a database
- Planned for an event to meet up with the project's ambassadors.

INTERNSHIP, ASSISTANT PROJECT MANAGER 07/2016 - 09/2016

Islamic Development Bank, Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

- Assisted the Knowledge Management & Innovation (KMI) Department, where I worked on a project that aimed to institutionalize the knowledge capital within the bank
- Created a KMI Knowledge Brief
- Conducted a business and a technical analysis of the Departmental Task Cente Platform
- Developed a Database Navigation Guide
- Validated the knowledge assets through meeting with stakeholders.

INTERNSHIP, APPLICATION DEVELOPER 05/2016 - 06/2016

Dallah IT solutions, Jeddah, Saudi Arabia

- Assisted with an app development project that aimed to provide small and mediumsized companies with an SAP alternative solution
- Participated in designing a database for the app
- Participated in developing an interface design for the app using Android Studio software

SKILLS

- Data Collection & Analysis
- Business Process Mapping
- Project Management
- Strategic Planning
- Change Management
- Workshop Facilitation

CERTIFICATIONS

- The Effective Facilitator, Leadership Strategies Institute (2022)
- EFQM Certified Foundation Training (2021)
- HR Specialist Skills Development, Royati Training Center (2020)
- SAP Certified Application Associate Business Process Integration (2017)

LANGUAGES Arabic: Native language

English: C1

Advanced